1 Who is the author of the book, "The Iron Lady: A Biography of <PERSON>Margaret Thatcher</PERSON>"?
2 What was the monetary value of the Nobel Peace Prize in 1989?
3 What does the <LOCATION>Peugeot</LOCATION> company manufacture?
4 How much did <ORGANIZATION>Mercury</ORGANIZATION> spend on advertising in 1993?
5 What is the name of the managing director of <ORGANIZATION>Apricot Computer</ORGANIZATION>?
6 Why did <PERSON>David Koresh</PERSON> ask the <ORGANIZATION>FBI</ORGANIZATION> for a word processor?
7 What debts did Qintex group leave?
8 What is the name of the rare neurological disease with symptoms such as: involuntary movements (tics), swearing, and incoherent vocalizations (grunts, shouts, etc.)?
9 How far is <LOCATION>Yaroslavl</LOCATION> from <LOCATION>Moscow</LOCATION>?
10 Name the designer of the shoe that spawned millions of plastic imitations, known as "jellies".
11 Who was President <LOCATION>Cleveland</LOCATION>'s wife?
12 How much did <ORGANIZATION>Manchester United</ORGANIZATION> spend on players in 1993?
13 How much could you rent a <ORGANIZATION>Volkswagen</ORGANIZATION> bug for in 1966?
15 When was <LOCATION>London</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Docklands Light Railway</ORGANIZATION> constructed?
16 What two <LOCATION>US</LOCATION> biochemists won the Nobel Prize in medicine in 1992?
17 How long did the <PERSON>Charles Manson</PERSON> murder trial last?
18 Who was the first Taiwanese President?
19 Who was the leader of the Branch Davidian Cult confronted by the <ORGANIZATION>FBI</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Waco</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> in 1993?
20 Where is <LOCATION>Inoco</LOCATION> based?
21 Who was the first <LOCATION>American</LOCATION> in space?
22 When did the Jurassic Period end?
23 When did <LOCATION>Spain</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Korea</LOCATION> start ambassadorial relations?
24 When did <PERSON>Nixon</PERSON> visit <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>?
25 Who was the lead actress in the movie "Sleepless in <LOCATION>Seattle</LOCATION>"?
26 What is the name of the "female" counterpart to <PERSON>El Nino</PERSON>, which results in cooling temperatures and very dry weather?
27 Where did the 6th annual meeting of <LOCATION>Indonesia-Malaysia</LOCATION> forest experts take place?
28 Who may be best known for breaking the color line in baseball?
29 What is the brightest star visible from <LOCATION>Earth</LOCATION>?
30 What are the <ORGANIZATION>Valdez</ORGANIZATION> Principles?
31 Where was <PERSON>Ulysses S. Grant</PERSON> born?
32 Who received the Will <ORGANIZATION>Rogers Award</ORGANIZATION> in 1989?
33 What is the largest city in <LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION>?
34 Where is the actress, <PERSON>Marion Davies</PERSON>, buried?
35 What is the name of the highest mountain in <LOCATION>Africa</LOCATION>?
36 In 1990, what day of the week did Christmas fall on?
37 What was the name of the <LOCATION>US</LOCATION> helicopter pilot shot down over <LOCATION>North Korea</LOCATION>?
38 Where was <PERSON>George Washington</PERSON> born?
39 Who was chosen to be the first black chairman of the military <ORGANIZATION>Joint Chiefs of Staff</ORGANIZATION>?
40 Who won the Nobel Peace Prize in 1991?
41 What is the legal blood alcohol limit for the state of <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>?
42 What was the target rate for M3 growth in 1992?
43 What costume designer decided that <PERSON>Michael Jackson</PERSON> should only wear one glove?
44 Who is the director of the international group called the <ORGANIZATION>Human Genome Organization</ORGANIZATION> (HUGO) that is trying to coordinate gene-mapping research worldwide?
45 When did <PERSON>Lucelly Garcia</PERSON>, a former ambassador of <ORGANIZATION>Columbia</ORGANIZATION> to <LOCATION>Honduras</LOCATION>, die?
46 Who is the mayor of <LOCATION>Marbella</LOCATION>?
47 What company is the largest Japanese ship builder?
48 Where is the massive <LOCATION>North Korean</LOCATION> nuclear complex located?
49 Who fired <PERSON>Maria Ybarra</PERSON> from her position in <LOCATION>San Diego</LOCATION> council?
50 When was <LOCATION>Dubai</LOCATION>'s first concrete house built?
51 Who is the president of <ORGANIZATION>Stanford University</ORGANIZATION>?
52 Who invented the road traffic <PERSON>cone</PERSON>?
54 When did <PERSON>Nixon</PERSON> die?
55 Where is <ORGANIZATION>Microsoft</ORGANIZATION>'s corporate headquarters located?
56 How many calories are there in a <ORGANIZATION>Big Mac</ORGANIZATION>?
57 What is the acronym for the rating system for air conditioner efficiency?
58 Name a film that has won the Golden Bear in the <LOCATION>Berlin</LOCATION> Film Festival?
59 Who was President of <LOCATION>Costa Rica</LOCATION> in 1994?
60 What is the fare cost for the round trip between <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> on Concorde?
61 What brand of white rum is still made in <LOCATION>Cuba</LOCATION>?
62 What is the name of the chronic neurological autoimmune disease which attacks the protein sheath that surrounds nerve cells causing a gradual loss of movement in the body?
63 What nuclear-powered Russian submarine sank in the <LOCATION>Norwegian Sea</LOCATION> on April 7, 1989?
64 Who is the voice of <ORGANIZATION>Miss Piggy</ORGANIZATION>?
65 Name a country that is developing a magnetic levitation railway system?
66 Name the first private citizen to fly in space.
68 What does <PERSON>El Nino</PERSON> mean in spanish?
69 Who came up with the name, <PERSON>El Nino</PERSON>? 
70 How many lives were lost in the <ORGANIZATION>China Airlines</ORGANIZATION>' crash in <LOCATION>Nagoya</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>?
71 In what year did <PERSON>Joe DiMaggio</PERSON> compile his 56-game hitting streak?
72 When did the original <PERSON>Howdy Doody</PERSON> show go off the air?
73 Where is the Taj Mahal?
74 Who leads the star ship <ORGANIZATION>Enterprise in Star Trek</ORGANIZATION>?
75 What cancer is commonly associated with AIDS?
76 In which year was <LOCATION>New Zealand</LOCATION> excluded from the <ORGANIZATION>ANZUS</ORGANIZATION> alliance?
77 Who played the part of the Godfather in the movie, "The Godfather"? 
78 Which large <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> city had the highest murder rate for 1988?
79 What did <PERSON>Shostakovich</PERSON> write for <PERSON>Rostropovich</PERSON>?
80 What is the name of the promising anticancer compound derived from the pacific yew tree?
81 How many inhabitants live in the town of <LOCATION>Ushuaia</LOCATION>?
82 How many consecutive baseball games did <PERSON>Lou Gehrig</PERSON> play?
83 What is the tallest building in <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>?
84 Which country is <LOCATION>Australia</LOCATION>'s largest export market?
85 Which former <ORGANIZATION>Ku Klux Klan</ORGANIZATION> member won an elected office in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>?
86 Who won two gold medals in skiing in the Olympic Games in <LOCATION>Calgary</LOCATION>?
87 Who followed <PERSON>Willy Brandt</PERSON> as chancellor of the <ORGANIZATION>Federal Republic</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION>?
88 What is <LOCATION>Grenada</LOCATION>'s main commodity export?
89 At what age did <ORGANIZATION>Rossini</ORGANIZATION> stop writing opera?
90 Who is the founder of <LOCATION>Scientology</LOCATION>?
91 Which city in <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> has the largest number of foreign financial companies?
92 Who released the Internet worm in the late 1980s?
93 Who first circumnavigated the globe?
94 Who wrote the song, "Stardust"?
96 What time of day did <ORGANIZATION>Emperor Hirohito</ORGANIZATION> die?
97 How large is the Arctic refuge to preserve unique wildlife and wilderness value on <LOCATION>Alaska</LOCATION>'s north coast?
98 Where is the highest point in <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>?
99 What is the term for the sum of all genetic material in a given organism?
100 What is considered the costliest disaster the insurance industry has ever faced?
101 How many people live in the Falklands?
102 Who is the Voyager project manager?
103 How many people died when the <LOCATION>Estonia</LOCATION> sank in 1994?
104 What language is most commonly used in <LOCATION>Bombay</LOCATION>?
105 How many people does <ORGANIZATION>Honda</ORGANIZATION> employ in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>?
106 What is the second highest mountain peak in the world?
107 When was <LOCATION>China</LOCATION>'s first nuclear test?
108 Which company created the Internet browser Mosaic?
109 Where does <PERSON>Buzz Aldrin</PERSON> want to build a permanent, manned space station?
110 Who killed <PERSON>Lee Harvey Oswald</PERSON>?
111 How long does it take to travel from <LOCATION>Tokyo</LOCATION> to <ORGANIZATION>Niigata</ORGANIZATION>?
112 Who is the President of <LOCATION>Ghana</LOCATION>?
113 What is the name of the medical condition in which a baby is born without a brain?
114 How much stronger is the new vitreous carbon material invented by the <ORGANIZATION>Tokyo Institute of Technology</ORGANIZATION> compared with the material made from cellulose?
115 What is <ORGANIZATION>Head Start</ORGANIZATION>?
116 Which team won the Super Bowl in 1968?
118 What percentage of the world's plant and animal species can be found in the <LOCATION>Amazon</LOCATION> forests?
119 What Nobel laureate was expelled from the <LOCATION>Philippines</LOCATION> before the conference on <LOCATION>East Timor</LOCATION>?
120 Who held the endurance record for women pilots in 1929?
121 Who won the first general election for President held in <LOCATION>Malawi</LOCATION> in May 1994?
122 Who is section manager for guidance and control systems at <ORGANIZATION>JPL</ORGANIZATION>?
123 How many Vietnamese were there in the <LOCATION>Soviet Union</LOCATION>?
124 What was Agent Orange used for during the <LOCATION>Vietnam</LOCATION> War?
125 In what city is the <ORGANIZATION>US Declaration of Independence</ORGANIZATION> located?
126 When did <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> begin turning the <LOCATION>Gaza Strip</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Jericho</LOCATION> over to the <ORGANIZATION>PLO</ORGANIZATION>?
127 Which city has the oldest relationship as a sister-city with <LOCATION>Los Angeles</LOCATION>?
128 Who was the second man to walk on the <LOCATION>moon</LOCATION>?
129 How many times was pitcher, <PERSON>Warren Spahn</PERSON>, a 20-game winner in his 21 major league seasons?
130 When was <LOCATION>Yemen</LOCATION> reunified?
131 Which Japanese car maker had its biggest percentage of sale in the domestic market?
132 What is the capital of <LOCATION>Uruguay</LOCATION>?
133 What is the name for the technique of growing certain plants in soils contaminated with toxic metals, wherein the plants take up the toxic metals, are harvested, and the metals recovered for recycling?
134 Where is it planned to berth the merchant ship, Lane Victory, which <ORGANIZATION>Merchant Marine</ORGANIZATION> veterans are converting into a floating museum?
135 What famous communist leader died in <LOCATION>Mexico City</LOCATION>?
136 Who is the <ORGANIZATION>Queen of Holland</ORGANIZATION>?
137 Who is the president of the <LOCATION>Spanish</LOCATION> government?
138 What is the name of the normal process in all living things, including humans, in which cells are programmed to "commit suicide"?
139 How many people did the <ORGANIZATION>United Nations</ORGANIZATION> commit to help restore order and distribute humanitarian relief in <LOCATION>Somalia</LOCATION> in September 1992?
141 What is the duration of the trip from <LOCATION>Bristol</LOCATION> to <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> by rail?
142 What is the population of <LOCATION>Ulan Bator</LOCATION>, capital of <LOCATION>Mongolia</LOCATION>?
143 Where does most of the marijuana entering the <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> come from?
144 How many megawatts will the power project in <LOCATION>Indonesia</LOCATION>, built by a consortium headed by <ORGANIZATION>Mission Energy</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>US</LOCATION>, produce?
145 What did <PERSON>John Hinckley</PERSON> do to impress <PERSON>Jodie Foster</PERSON>?
147 Who is the prime minister of <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>?
148 How many soldiers were involved in the last <LOCATION>Panama</LOCATION> invasion by the <LOCATION>United States of America</LOCATION>?
149 Where is the <ORGANIZATION>Bulls</ORGANIZATION> basketball team based?
150 What is the length of border between the <LOCATION>Ukraine</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Russia</LOCATION>?
151 Where did <PERSON>Dylan Thomas</PERSON> die?
152 How many people live in <LOCATION>Tokyo</LOCATION>?
153 What is the capital of <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>?
154 How many Grand Slam titles did <PERSON>Bjorn Borg</PERSON> win?
155 Who was the <ORGANIZATION>Democratic</ORGANIZATION> nominee in the <LOCATION>American</LOCATION> presidential election?
156 When was General <PERSON>Manuel Noriega</PERSON> ousted as the leader of <LOCATION>Panama</LOCATION> and turned over to <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> authorities?
157 Where is  <ORGANIZATION>Dartmouth College</ORGANIZATION>?
158 How many mines can still be found in the <LOCATION>Falklands</LOCATION> after the war ended?
159 Why are electric cars less efficient in the north-east than in <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>?
160 When did French revolutionaries storm the Bastille?
161 How rich is <PERSON>Bill Gates</PERSON>?
162 What is the capital of <LOCATION>Kosovo</LOCATION>?
163 What state does <PERSON>Charles Robb</PERSON> represent?
164 Who is the leading competitor of <ORGANIZATION>Trans Union Company</ORGANIZATION>?
165 Which type of submarine was bought recently by <LOCATION>South Korea</LOCATION>?
166 When did communist control end in <LOCATION>Hungary</LOCATION>?
167 What nationality is Pope <PERSON>John Paul II</PERSON>?
168 Who was the captain of the tanker, <ORGANIZATION>Exxon Valdez</ORGANIZATION>, involved in the oil spill in <LOCATION>Prince William Sound</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Alaska</LOCATION>, 1989?
169 Whom did the <ORGANIZATION>Chicago Bulls</ORGANIZATION> beat in the 1993 championship?
170 Who was President of <LOCATION>Afghanistan</LOCATION> in 1994?
171 Who is the director of intergovernmental affairs for the <LOCATION>San Diego county</LOCATION>?
172 Where is the <ORGANIZATION>Keck</ORGANIZATION> telescope?
173 How many moons does <LOCATION>Jupiter</LOCATION> have?
174 When did <PERSON>Jaco Pastorius</PERSON> die?
175 When did beethoven die?
176 How many people in <LOCATION>Tucson</LOCATION>?
177 How tall is Mt. Everest?
178 What is the capital of <LOCATION>Congo</LOCATION>?
179 What is the capital of <LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION>?
180 What is the capital of <LOCATION>Sri Lanka</LOCATION>?
181 What novel inspired the movie BladeRunner?
182 What was the first <PERSON>Gilbert</PERSON> and <PERSON>Sullivan</PERSON> opera?
183 What was the name of the computer in "2001: A Space Odyssey"?
184 When was <PERSON>Queen Victoria</PERSON> born?
185 When was the battle of the <ORGANIZATION>Somme</ORGANIZATION> fought?
186 Where did the Battle of the Bulge take place?
187 Where was <PERSON>Lincoln</PERSON> assassinated?
188 When was the women's suffrage amendment ratified?
189 Where is <LOCATION>Qatar</LOCATION>?
190 Where is South Bend?
191 Where was <PERSON>Harry Truman</PERSON> born?
192 Who was Secretary of <ORGANIZATION>State</ORGANIZATION> during the <PERSON>Nixon</PERSON> administration?
194 Who wrote "The Pines of <LOCATION>Rome</LOCATION>"?
195 Who wrote "Dubliners"? 
196 Who wrote "Hamlet"?
197 What did <PERSON>Richard Feynman</PERSON> say upon hearing he would receive the Nobel Prize in Physics?
198 How did <LOCATION>Socrates</LOCATION> die?
199 How tall is the Matterhorn?
200 How tall is the replica of the <ORGANIZATION>Matterhorn</ORGANIZATION> at Disneyland?
201 What was the name of the first <LOCATION>Russian</LOCATION> astronaut to do a spacewalk?
202 Where is <LOCATION>Belize</LOCATION> located?
203 How much folic acid should an expectant mother get daily?
204 What type of bridge is the <LOCATION>Golden Gate Bridge</LOCATION>?
205 What is the population of the <LOCATION>Bahamas</LOCATION>?
206 How far away is the <LOCATION>moon</LOCATION>?
207 What is <PERSON>Francis Scott Key</PERSON> best known for?
208 What state has the most Indians?
209 Who invented the paper clip?
210 How many dogs pull a sled in the Iditarod?
211 Where did bocci originate?
212 Who invented the electric guitar?
213 Name a flying mammal.
214 How many hexagons are on a soccer ball?
215 Who is the leader of <LOCATION>India</LOCATION>?
216 What is the primary language of the <LOCATION>Philippines</LOCATION>?
217 What is the habitat of the chickadee?
218 Who was <PERSON>Whitcomb Judson</PERSON>?
219 What is the population of <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>?
220 Who is the prime minister of <LOCATION>Australia</LOCATION>?
221 Who killed <PERSON>Martin Luther King</PERSON>?
222 Who is <PERSON>Anubis</PERSON>?
223 Where's <LOCATION>Montenegro</LOCATION>?
224 What does laser stand for?
225 Who is the Greek God of the Sea?
226 Where is the <LOCATION>Danube</LOCATION>? 
227 Where does dew come from?
228 What is platinum?
229 Who is the fastest swimmer in the world?
230 When did the vesuvius last erupt?
231 Who was the president of <LOCATION>Vichy France</LOCATION>?
232 Who invented television?
233 Who made the first airplane?
234 Who made the first airplane that could fly?
235 How many astronauts have been on the <LOCATION>moon</LOCATION>?
236 Who is <PERSON>Coronado</PERSON>?
237 Name one of the major gods of <LOCATION>Hinduism</LOCATION>?
238 What does the abbreviation <ORGANIZATION>OAS</ORGANIZATION> stand for?
239 Who is <PERSON>Barbara Jordan</PERSON>?
240 How many years ago did the ship Titanic sink?
241 What is a caldera?
242 What was the name of the famous battle in 1836 between <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Mexico</LOCATION>?
243 Where did the ukulele originate?
244 Who invented baseball?
245 Where can you find the <LOCATION>Venus</LOCATION> flytrap?
246 What did <ORGANIZATION>Vasco da Gama</ORGANIZATION> discover?
247 Who won the <ORGANIZATION>Battle of Gettysburg</ORGANIZATION>?
248 What is the largest snake in the world?
249 Where is the <ORGANIZATION>Valley of the Kings</ORGANIZATION>?
250 Where did the <LOCATION>Maya</LOCATION> people live?
251 How many people live in <LOCATION>Chile</LOCATION>?
252 When was the first flush toilet invented?
253 Who is <PERSON>William Wordsworth</PERSON>?
254 What is <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>'s state bird?
255 Who thought of teaching people to tie their shoe laces?
256 Who is buried in the great pyramid of <LOCATION>Giza</LOCATION>?
257 What do penguins eat?
258 Where do lobsters like to live?
259 What are birds descendents of?
260 What does <ORGANIZATION>NAFTA</ORGANIZATION> stand for?
261 What company sells the most greeting cards?
262 What is the name of the longest ruling dynasty of <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>?
263 When was <PERSON>Babe Ruth</PERSON> born?
264 Who wrote the Farmer's Almanac?
265 What's the farthest planet from the sun?
266 Where was <PERSON>Pythagoras</PERSON> born?
267 What is the name for clouds that produce rain?
268 Who killed <PERSON>Caesar</PERSON>?
269 Who was <PERSON>Picasso</PERSON>?
270 Where is the Orinoco?
271 How tall is the giraffe?
272 Where are there aborigines?
273 Who was the first <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> president ever to resign?
274 Who invented the game Scrabble?
275 About how many soldiers died in World War II?
276 How much money does the Sultan of <LOCATION>Brunei</LOCATION> have?
277 How large is <LOCATION>Missouri</LOCATION>'s population?
278 What was the death toll at the eruption of <LOCATION>Mount Pinatubo</LOCATION>?
279 Who was <PERSON>Lacan</PERSON>?
280 What's the tallest building in <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION>?
281 When did <PERSON>Geraldine Ferraro</PERSON> run for vice president?
282 What do ladybugs eat?
283 Where is <PERSON>Ayer</PERSON>'s rock?
284 What is the life expectancy of an elephant?
285 When was the first railroad from the east coast to the west coast completed?
286 What is the nickname of <LOCATION>Pennsylvania</LOCATION>?
287 Who is <PERSON>Desmond Tutu</PERSON>?
288 How fast can a Corvette go?
289 What are <PERSON>John C. Calhoun</PERSON> and <PERSON>Henry Clay</PERSON> known as?
290 When was Hurricane <PERSON>Hugo</PERSON>?
291 When did the <LOCATION>Carolingian</LOCATION> period begin? 
292 How big is <LOCATION>Australia</LOCATION>?
293 Who found <LOCATION>Hawaii</LOCATION>?
294 Who is the richest person in the world?
295 How many films did <PERSON>Ingmar Bergman</PERSON> make?
296 What is the federal minimum wage?
297 What did brontosauruses eat?
298 What is <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>'s state tree?
299 How many types of lemurs are there?
300 What is leukemia?
301 Who was the first coach of the <ORGANIZATION>Cleveland Browns</ORGANIZATION>?
302 How many people die from snakebite poisoning in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> per year?
303 Who is the prophet of the religion of <LOCATION>Islam</LOCATION>?
304 Where is <ORGANIZATION>Tornado Alley</ORGANIZATION>?
305 What is molybdenum?
306 Where do hyenas live?
307 Who is <PERSON>Peter Weir</PERSON>?
308 How many home runs did <PERSON>Babe Ruth</PERSON> hit in his lifetime?
309 Who was <ORGANIZATION>Buffalo Bill</ORGANIZATION>?
310 Where is the bridge over the river <PERSON>Kwai</PERSON>?
311 How many Superbowls have the 49ers won?
312 Who was the architect of Central Park?
313 Who invented paper?
314 What is <PERSON>Alice Cooper</PERSON>'s real name?
315 Why can't ostriches fly?
316 Name a tiger that is extinct?
317 Where is <LOCATION>Guam</LOCATION>?
318 Where did <PERSON>Bill Gates</PERSON> go to college?
319 How many continents are there?
320 Where is <LOCATION>Romania</LOCATION> located?
322 Who was the first king of <LOCATION>England</LOCATION>?
323 Who is the richest woman in the world?
324 What is <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>'s capital?
325 What is the size of <LOCATION>Argentina</LOCATION>?
326 What do manatees eat?
327 When was the <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> fire?
328 What was the man's name who was killed in a duel with <PERSON>Aaron Burr</PERSON>?
329 What is the population of <LOCATION>Mexico</LOCATION>?
330 When was the slinky invented?
331 How hot is the core of the earth?
332 How long would it take to get from <LOCATION>Earth</LOCATION> to <LOCATION>Mars</LOCATION>?
333 What is the name of the second space shuttle?
334 How old is the sun?
335 What is the wingspan of a condor?
336 When was <ORGANIZATION>Microsoft</ORGANIZATION> established?
337 What's the average salary of a professional baseball player?
338 Who invented basketball?
339 What was the ball game of ancient Mayans called?
340 Who is <PERSON>Zebulon Pike</PERSON>?
341 How wide is the <LOCATION>Atlantic Ocean</LOCATION>?
342 What effect does a prism have on light?
343 What's the longest river in the world?
344 Who was considered to be the father of psychology?
345 What is the population of <LOCATION>Kansas</LOCATION>?
346 Who is <PERSON>Langston Hughes</PERSON>?
347 Who was <PERSON>Monet</PERSON>?
348 Who built the first pyramid?
349 What is the best-selling book of all time?
350 How many Stradivarius violins were ever made?
351 Who is <PERSON>Charles Lindbergh</PERSON>?
352 Who invented the game bowling?
353 The numbering system we use today was introduced to the western world by what culture?
354 What is a nematode?
355 What is the most expensive car in the world?
356 Where does chocolate come from?
357 What state in the <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> covers the largest area?
358 What is a meerkat?
359 Where is <LOCATION>Melbourne</LOCATION>?
360 How much in miles is a ten K run?
361 How hot does the inside of an active volcano get?
362 What is the capital of <LOCATION>Burkina Faso</LOCATION>?
363 What is the capital of <LOCATION>Haiti</LOCATION>?
364 How many people lived in <LOCATION>Nebraska</LOCATION> in the mid 1980s?
365 What is the population of <LOCATION>Mozambique</LOCATION>?
366 Who won the Superbowl in 1982?
367 What is <PERSON>Martin Luther King Jr.</PERSON>'s real birthday?
368 Where is <LOCATION>Trinidad</LOCATION>?
369 Where did the Inuits live?
370 What is the most common cancer?
371 A corgi is a kind of what?
372 When was the <ORGANIZATION>Triangle Shirtwaist</ORGANIZATION> fire?
373 Where is the <LOCATION>Kalahari</LOCATION> desert?
374 What is <LOCATION>porphyria</LOCATION>?
375 What ocean did the Titanic sink in?
377 At what speed does the <LOCATION>Earth</LOCATION> revolve around the sun?
378 Who is the emperor of <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION>?
379 How big is our galaxy in diameter?
380 What language is mostly spoken in <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION>?
381 Who assassinated President <PERSON>McKinley</PERSON>?
382 When did <PERSON>Muhammad</PERSON> live?
383 What is the largest variety of cactus?
384 Who invented the radio?
385 Where are zebras most likely found?
386 What is anorexia nervosa?
387 What year did <LOCATION>Montana</LOCATION> become a state? 
388 What were the names of the three ships used by <LOCATION>Columbus</LOCATION>?
389 Who was the 21st <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> President?
390 Where was <PERSON>John Adams</PERSON> born?
391 Who painted <PERSON>Olympia</PERSON>?
392 Who was <PERSON>Quetzalcoatl</PERSON>?
393 Where is your corpus callosum?
395 What is saltpeter?
396 Who invented silly putty?
397 When was the <LOCATION>Brandenburg Gate</LOCATION> in <LOCATION>Berlin</LOCATION> built?
398 When is Boxing Day?
399 What is the exchange rate between <LOCATION>England</LOCATION> and the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>?
400 What is the name of the Jewish alphabet?
401 Who was <PERSON>Maria Theresa</PERSON>?
402 What nationality was <PERSON>Jackson Pollock</PERSON>?
403 Tell me what city the <LOCATION>Kentucky Horse Park</LOCATION> is near?
404 What is the state nickname of <LOCATION>Mississippi</LOCATION>?
405 Who used to make cars with rotary engines?
406 What is the tallest mountain?
407 What is <LOCATION>Black Hills</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>South Dakota</LOCATION> most famous for?
408 What kind of animal was <PERSON>Winnie</PERSON> the <PERSON>Pooh</PERSON>?
409 What's another name for aspartame?
410 What does hazmat stand for?
411 What tourist attractions are there in <LOCATION>Reims</LOCATION>?
412 Name a film in which Jude Law acted.
413 Where are the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> headquarters for <ORGANIZATION>Procter & Gamble</ORGANIZATION>?
414 What's the formal name for <PERSON>Lou Gehrig</PERSON>'s disease?
415 What does <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION> stand for?
416 When was <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION>'s first broadcast?
417 Who owns <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION>?
418 What is the name of a <LOCATION>Salt Lake City</LOCATION> newspaper?
419 Who was <PERSON>Jane Goodall</PERSON>?
420 What is pandoro?
421 What is thalassemia?
422 When did Princess <PERSON>Diana</PERSON> and <PERSON>Prince Charles</PERSON> get married?
423 What soft drink contains the largest amount of caffeine?
424 What do you call a group of geese?
425 How many months does a normal human pregnancy last?
426 What format was <ORGANIZATION>VHS</ORGANIZATION>'s main competition?
427 What culture developed the idea of potlatch?
428 Where is <LOCATION>Logan International</LOCATION> located?
429 What university was <PERSON>Woodrow Wilson</PERSON> President of?
430 Where is Basque country located?
431 What does <ORGANIZATION>CPR</ORGANIZATION> stand for?
432 What state produces the best lobster to eat?
433 Who was <ORGANIZATION>Darth Vader</ORGANIZATION>'s son?
434 What is a nanometer?
435 How did <PERSON>Bob Marley</PERSON> die?
436 What instrument is <PERSON>Ray Charles</PERSON> best known for playing?
437 What is <PERSON>Dick Clark</PERSON>'s birthday?
438 What is titanium?
439 What is "Nine Inch Nails"?
440 Where was <PERSON>Poe</PERSON> born?
441 What king was forced to agree to the <ORGANIZATION>Magna Carta</ORGANIZATION>?
442 What's the name of <LOCATION>Pittsburgh</LOCATION>'s baseball team?
443 What is the chemical formula/name for napalm?
444 Where is the location of the <ORGANIZATION>Orange Bowl</ORGANIZATION>?
445 When was the last major eruption of <LOCATION>Mount St.</LOCATION> Helens?
446 What is the abbreviation for <ORGANIZATION>Original Equipment Manufacturer</ORGANIZATION>?
447 What is anise?
448 Where is <ORGANIZATION>Rider College</ORGANIZATION> located?
449 What does <PERSON>Nicholas Cage</PERSON> do for a living?
450 What does caliente mean (in English)?
451 Where is <LOCATION>McCarren Airport</LOCATION>?
452 Who created "The Muppets"?
453 When is Bastille Day?
454 What is the Islamic counterpart to the <ORGANIZATION>Red Cross</ORGANIZATION>?
455 What is <PERSON>Colin Powell</PERSON> best known for?
456 What is the busiest air travel season?
457 Where is <ORGANIZATION>Webster University</ORGANIZATION>?
458 What's the name of a golf course in <LOCATION>Myrtle Beach</LOCATION>?
459 When was <PERSON>John D. Rockefeller</PERSON> born?
460 Name a Gaelic language.
461 Who was the author of the book about computer hackers called "The Cuckoo's Egg: Tracking a Spy Through the Maze of <ORGANIZATION>Computer Espionage</ORGANIZATION>"?
462 What is measured in curies?
463 What is a stratocaster?
464 Where are the headquarters of <ORGANIZATION>Eli Lilly</ORGANIZATION>?
465 Where did <PERSON>Hillary Clinton</PERSON> graduate college?
466 Where is <LOCATION>Glasgow</LOCATION>?
467 Who was <PERSON>Samuel Johnsons</PERSON>'s friend and biographer?
468 What is tyvek?
469 Who coined the term "cyberspace" in his novel "Neuromancer"?
470 Who is the president of <LOCATION>Bolivia</LOCATION>?
471 What year did <PERSON>Hitler</PERSON> die?
472 When did the American Civil War end?
473 Who created the character of Scrooge?
474 Who first broke the sound barrier?
475 What is the salary of a <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Representative?
477 What are the birth dates for scorpios?
478 What is the airport code for <ORGANIZATION>Los Angeles International</ORGANIZATION>?
479 Who provides telephone service in <LOCATION>Orange County</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>?
480 What is the zip code for <LOCATION>Fremont</LOCATION>, CA?
481 Who shot <PERSON>Billy</PERSON> the Kid?
482 Who is the monarch of the <LOCATION>United Kingdom</LOCATION>?
483 What is sake?
484 What is the name of the Lion King's son in the movie, "The Lion King"?
485 Where is <LOCATION>Amsterdam</LOCATION>?
486 How many states have a "lemon law" for new automobiles?
487 What was the name of the movie that starred <PERSON>Sharon Stone</PERSON> and <PERSON>Arnold Schwarzenegger</PERSON>?
488 What continent is <LOCATION>Bolivia</LOCATION> on?
489 What are the <ORGANIZATION>Poconos</ORGANIZATION>?
490 Where did guinea pigs originate?
492 What is the name of the vaccine for chicken pox?
493 What is <PERSON>Betsy Ross</PERSON> famous for?
494 Who wrote the book, "The Grinch Who Stole Christmas"?
495 When did <PERSON>Aldous Huxley</PERSON> write, "Brave New World"?
496 Who wrote the book, "Song of Solomon"?
497 Who portrayed <PERSON>Jake</PERSON> in the television show, "<PERSON>Jake</PERSON> and the Fatman"?
498 Who portrayed Fatman in the television show, "<PERSON>Jake</PERSON> and the Fatman"?
499 Where is <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION>?
500 What city in <LOCATION>Florida is Sea World</LOCATION> in?
501 What is the population of <LOCATION>Ohio</LOCATION>?
502 What is one of the cities that the <ORGANIZATION>University of Minnesota</ORGANIZATION> is located in?
503 What kind of sports team is the <ORGANIZATION>Buffalo Sabres</ORGANIZATION>?
504 Who is the founder of the <ORGANIZATION>Wal-Mart</ORGANIZATION> stores?
505 What city is <LOCATION>Massachusetts General Hospital</LOCATION> located in?
506 Who reports the weather on the "Good Morning America" television show?
507 When did the <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> lottery begin?
508 Where is <LOCATION>Los Vegas</LOCATION>?
509 When was <PERSON>Beethoven</PERSON> born?
510 What's the name of the tiger that advertises for Frosted Flakes cereal?
511 Where is <ORGANIZATION>Tufts University</ORGANIZATION>?
512 What movie did <PERSON>Madilyn Kahn</PERSON> star in with <PERSON>Gene Wilder</PERSON>?
513 When did the royal wedding of Prince <PERSON>Andrew</PERSON> and <ORGANIZATION>Fergie</ORGANIZATION> take place?
514 What cereal goes "snap, crackle, pop"?
515 For what disease is the drug Sinemet used as a treatment?
516 Who is <PERSON>Henry Butler</PERSON>?
517 What province is <LOCATION>Edmonton</LOCATION> located in?
518 In what area of the world was the Six Day War fought?
519 What is the zip code for <LOCATION>Parsippany</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>NJ</LOCATION>?
520 When was the first <LOCATION>Barbie</LOCATION> produced?
521 What was the distinguishing mark on the "Little Rascals" dog?
522 What does <ORGANIZATION>EKG</ORGANIZATION> stand for?
523 What is Chiricahua the name of?
524 Where did Wicca first develop?
525 Name a symptom of mononucleosis.
526 Where are diamonds mined?
527 When was the <ORGANIZATION>NFL</ORGANIZATION> established?
528 What are geckos?
529 Who is <PERSON>Terrence Malick</PERSON>?
530 What other name were the "Little Rascals" known as?
531 What was the name of the "Little Rascals" dog?
532 What breed of dog was the "Little Rascals" dog?
533 Who won the rugby world cup in 1987?
534 Where is <ORGANIZATION>Windsor Castle</ORGANIZATION>?
535 Who portrayed "<PERSON>Rosanne Rosanna-Dana</PERSON>" on the television show "Saturday Night Live"?
536 What is the population of the <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION>?
537 What animal do buffalo wings come from?
538 When was the bar-code invented?
539 What is witch <PERSON>hazel</PERSON>?
540 What's the abbreviation for limited partnership?
541 What was the purpose of the <LOCATION>Manhattan</LOCATION> project?
542 What is the most common kind of skin cancer in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>?
543 Name a civil war battlefield.
544 What are pomegranates?
545 Who wrote the song, "Silent Night"?
546 Who portrayed "the man without a face" in the movie of the same name?
547 When was the Hoover Dam constructed?
548 What's the most famous tourist attraction in <LOCATION>Rome</LOCATION>?
549 At Christmas time, what is the traditional thing to do under the mistletoe?
550 What is the <LOCATION>Pennsylvania</LOCATION> state income tax rate?
551 What is the name of the <LOCATION>Michelangelo</LOCATION> painting that shows two hands with fingers touching?
552 What caused the <ORGANIZATION>Lynmouth</ORGANIZATION> floods?
553 What is the name of the company that manufactures the "American Girl" doll collection?
554 How many zip codes are there in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>?
555 What was the name of the Titanic's captain?
556 How many copies of an album must be sold for it to be a gold album?
557 When is the <ORGANIZATION>Tulip Festival</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Michigan</LOCATION>?
558 What is <ORGANIZATION>Giorgio Vasari</ORGANIZATION> famous for?
559 Who created the character <PERSON>James Bond</PERSON>?
560 What store does <PERSON>Martha Stewart</PERSON> advertise for?
561 Name an American made motorcycle.
562 What <ORGANIZATION>Cruise Line</ORGANIZATION> does <PERSON>Kathie Lee Gifford</PERSON> advertise for?
563 Name a movie that the actress, <PERSON>Sandra Bullock</PERSON>, had a role in.
564 Where is the <PERSON>Thomas Edison Museum</PERSON>?
565 What is <ORGANIZATION>TCI</ORGANIZATION>?
566 What state does MO stand for?
567 Name a female figure skater.
568 What state is the Filenes store located in?
569 How much calcium should an adult female have daily?
570 What hockey team did <PERSON>Wayne Gretzky</PERSON> play for?
571 What hair color can I use to just cover a little gray?
572 How long would it take for a $50 savings bond to mature?
573 How many home runs did <PERSON>Lou Gehrig</PERSON> have during his career?
574 How many states have a lottery?
575 What kind of a sports team is the <LOCATION>Wisconsin</LOCATION> Badgers?
576 What is the name of <PERSON>Joan Jett</PERSON>'s band?
577 Can you give me the name of a clock maker in <LOCATION>London</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>England</LOCATION>?
578 What was the name of the sitcom that <PERSON>Alyssa Milano</PERSON> starred in with <PERSON>Tony Danza</PERSON>?
579 What is the real name of the singer, <PERSON>Madonna</PERSON>?
580 Where did yoga originate?
581 What flower did <PERSON>Vincent Van Gogh</PERSON> paint?
582 What radio station did <PERSON>Paul Harvey</PERSON> work for?
583 What's the name of the song <PERSON>Will Smith</PERSON> sings about parents?
584 What does <ORGANIZATION>NASA</ORGANIZATION> stand for?
585 What famous model was married to <PERSON>Billy Joel</PERSON>?
586 What is the chemical symbol for nitrogen?
587 In what book can I find the story of Aladdin?
588 When did World War I start?
589 What state is <LOCATION>Niagra Falls</LOCATION> located in?
590 What's the name of the actress who starred in the movie, "Silence of the Lambs"?
591 Who owns the <ORGANIZATION>St. Louis Rams</ORGANIZATION>?
592 Where could I go to take a ride on a steam locomotive?
593 When was the movie, <LOCATION>Caligula</LOCATION>, made?
594 Name an <LOCATION>American</LOCATION> war plane?
595 Where is <LOCATION>Burma</LOCATION>?
596 How many highway miles to the gallon can you get with the <ORGANIZATION>Ford Fiesta</ORGANIZATION>?
597 Name a novel written by <PERSON>John Steinbeck</PERSON>.
598 Who wrote the song, "Boys of Summer"?
600 What is typhoid fever?
601 When did the neanderthal man live?
602 Who manufactures the software, "PhotoShop"?
603 How many casinos are in <LOCATION>Atlantic City</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>NJ</LOCATION>?
604 What state does <PERSON>Martha Stewart</PERSON> live in?
605 Who was the first woman in space?
606 What are <PERSON>Cushman</PERSON> and <PERSON>Wakefield</PERSON> known for?
607 What is <PERSON>D.B. Cooper</PERSON> known for?
608 When was <PERSON>Nostradamus</PERSON> born?
609 When was "the Great Depression"?
610 What is <ORGANIZATION>Archimedes</ORGANIZATION> famous for?
611 What is the medical condition of hypertension?
612 Who created the comic strip, "Garfield"?
613 Where is the Isle of Man?
614 Who wrote the book, "<PERSON>Huckleberry Finn</PERSON>"?
615 What day is known as the "national day of prayer"?
616 What is the purpose of a car bra?
617 What are chloroplasts?
618 What is the name of the art of growing miniature trees?
619 What is the telephone number for the <ORGANIZATION>University of Kentucky</ORGANIZATION>?
620 Who wrote "The Scarlet Letter"?
621 Name an art gallery in <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>.
622 What type of hunting are retrievers used for?
623 What party was <PERSON>Winston Churchill</PERSON> a member of?
624 How was <ORGANIZATION>Teddy Roosevelt</ORGANIZATION> related to <ORGANIZATION>FDR</ORGANIZATION>?
625 When did the <LOCATION>Chernobyl</LOCATION> nuclear accident occur?
626 What does SIDS stand for?
627 What's the name of the star of the cooking show, "Galloping Gourmet"?
628 What city is 94.5 <ORGANIZATION>KDGE Radio</ORGANIZATION> located in?
629 What President became Chief Justice after his presidency?
630 How tall is kilamanjaro?
631 Who won the nobel prize in literature in 1988?
632 What's the name of the <LOCATION>Tampa</LOCATION> newspaper?
633 How long do hermit crabs live?
634 What is <PERSON>Dr. Ruth</PERSON>'s last name?
635 What is cribbage?
636 <LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION> is the largest producer of what?
637 What wrestling star became "The Incredible Hulk"?
638 Who wrote "The Pit and the Pendulum"?
639 Who manufacturers <ORGANIZATION>Magic Chef</ORGANIZATION> applicances?
640 When was the first Wall Street Journal published?
641 What is the normal resting heart rate of a healthy adult?
642 Who's the lead singer of the Led Zeppelin band?
643 Who wrote "An Ideal Husband"?
644 What is ouzo?
645 When did the <ORGANIZATION>Dow</ORGANIZATION> first reach 2000?
646 Who was <PERSON>Charles Lindbergh</PERSON>'s wife?
647 How many miles is it from <LOCATION>London</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>England</LOCATION> to <LOCATION>Plymouth</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>England</LOCATION>?
649 Who played the teacher in Dead Poet's Society?
650 How many counties are in <LOCATION>Indiana</LOCATION>?
651 What actress starred in "The <LOCATION>Lion</LOCATION> in Winter"?
652 Where was <PERSON>Tesla</PERSON> born?
653 What's the name of a hotel in <LOCATION>Indianapolis</LOCATION>?
654 What <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Government agency registers trademarks?
655 Who started the <ORGANIZATION>Dominos Pizza</ORGANIZATION> chain?
656 What is the hair style called that new military recruits receive?
657 In what country is a stuck-out tongue a friendly greeting?
658 Where is <ORGANIZATION>Kings Canyon</ORGANIZATION>?
659 Where is the <PERSON>Mayo Clinic</PERSON>?
660 How big is the <ORGANIZATION>Electoral College</ORGANIZATION>?
661 How much does one ton of cement cost?
662 Where does <PERSON>Mother Angelica</PERSON> live?
663 How many people watch network television?
664 What is the name of a <LOCATION>Greek</LOCATION> god?
665 What year was the first automobile manufactured?
666 What's the population of <LOCATION>Mississippi</LOCATION>?
667 What was the name of <PERSON>Jacques Cousteau</PERSON>'s ship?
668 What are the names of <PERSON>Jacques Cousteau</PERSON>'s two sons?
669 What is Java?
670 What does Final Four refer to in the sports world?
671 What does <ORGANIZATION>Knight Ridder</ORGANIZATION> publish?
672 What task does the <PERSON>Bouvier</PERSON> breed of dog perform?
673 What sport do the <ORGANIZATION>Cleaveland Cavaliers</ORGANIZATION> play?
674 What year was the <PERSON>Avery Dennison</PERSON> company founded?
675 What's the population of <LOCATION>Biloxi</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Mississippi</LOCATION>?
676 Name a ballet company <PERSON>Mikhail Baryshnikov</PERSON> has danced for?
677 What was the name of the television show, staring <PERSON>Karl Malden</PERSON>, that had <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> in the title?
678 Who was the founding member of the <ORGANIZATION>Pink Floyd</ORGANIZATION> band?
679 What did <PERSON>Delilah</PERSON> do to <PERSON>Samson</PERSON>'s hair?
680 What's the name of the <ORGANIZATION>Tokyo Stock Exchange</ORGANIZATION>?
681 What actor first portrayed <PERSON>James Bond</PERSON>?
682 What type of horses appear on the Budweiser commercials?
683 What do river otters eat?
684 When did the art of quilting begin?
685 When did <ORGANIZATION>Amtrak</ORGANIZATION> begin operations?
686 Where is the <ORGANIZATION>Smithsonian Institute</ORGANIZATION> located?
687 What year did the Vietnam War end?
688 What country are <ORGANIZATION>Godiva</ORGANIZATION> chocolates from?
689 How many islands does <LOCATION>Fiji</LOCATION> have?
690 What card company sells Christmas ornaments?
691 Who manufactures synthroid?
692 What year was <PERSON>Desmond Mpilo Tutu</PERSON> awarded the Nobel Peace Prize?
693 What city did the <LOCATION>Flintstones</LOCATION> live in?
694 Who was the oldest <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> president?
695 Who was the tallest <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> president?
696 Where is <LOCATION>Santa Lucia</LOCATION>?
697 Which <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> President is buried in <LOCATION>Washington</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>D.C.</LOCATION>?
698 Where is <PERSON>Ocho Rios</PERSON>?
699 What year was <PERSON>Janet Jackson</PERSON>'s first album released?
700 What is another name for nearsightedness?
701 Winnie the <ORGANIZATION>Pooh</ORGANIZATION> is what kind of animal?  
702 What species was <PERSON>Winnie</PERSON> the <PERSON>Pooh</PERSON>?
703 Winnie the <ORGANIZATION>Pooh</ORGANIZATION> is an imitation of which animal?
704 What was the species of Winnie the <PERSON>Pooh</PERSON>?
705 <LOCATION>Aspartame</LOCATION> is also known as what?
706 What is a synonym for aspartame?
707 <LOCATION>Aspartame</LOCATION> is known by what other name?
708 <LOCATION>Aspartame</LOCATION> is also called what?
709 Hazmat stands for what?
710 What is the definition of hazmat?
711 What are the names of the tourist attractions in <LOCATION>Reims</LOCATION>?
712 What do most tourists visit in <LOCATION>Reims</LOCATION>?
713 What attracts tourists to <LOCATION>Reims</LOCATION>?
714 What are tourist attractions in <LOCATION>Reims</LOCATION>?
715 What could I see in <LOCATION>Reims</LOCATION>?
716 What is worth seeing in <LOCATION>Reims</LOCATION>?
717 What can one see in <LOCATION>Reims</LOCATION>?
718 Jude Law was in what movie?
719 Jude Law acted in which film?
720 What is a film starring <PERSON>Jude Law</PERSON>?
721 What film was <ORGANIZATION>Jude Law</ORGANIZATION> in?
722 What film or films has Jude Law appeared in?
723 What city houses the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> headquarters of <PERSON>Procter</PERSON> and <PERSON>Gamble</PERSON>?
724 Where is <ORGANIZATION>Procter & Gamble</ORGANIZATION> headquartered in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>?
725 What is the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> location of <ORGANIZATION>Procter & Gamble</ORGANIZATION> corporate offices?
726 <ORGANIZATION>Procter & Gamble</ORGANIZATION> is headquartered in which <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> city?
727 Where is <ORGANIZATION>Procter & Gamble</ORGANIZATION> based in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION>?
728 What is the recommended daily requirement for folic acid for pregnant women?
729 How much folic acid should a pregnant woman get each day?
730 What is the daily requirement of folic acid for an expectant mother?
731 What amount of folic acid should an expectant mother take daily?
732 Name the first <LOCATION>Russian</LOCATION> astronaut to do a spacewalk.
733 Who was the first <LOCATION>Russian</LOCATION> astronaut to walk in space?
734 Who was the first Russian to do a spacewalk?
735 <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION> is the abbreviation for what?
736 <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION> is an acronym for what?
737 What was the date of <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION>'s first broadcast?
738 CNN began broadcasting in what year?
739 <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION>'s first broadcast occurred on what date?
740 When did <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION> begin broadcasting?
741 When did <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION> go on the air?
742 Who is the owner of <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION>?
743 <ORGANIZATION>CNN</ORGANIZATION> is owned by whom?
744 What newspaper serves <LOCATION>Salt Lake City</LOCATION>?
745 Name a <LOCATION>Salt Lake City</LOCATION> newspaper.
746 What is <PERSON>Jane Goodall</PERSON> famous for?
747 What is <PERSON>Jane Goodall</PERSON> known for?
748 Why is <PERSON>Jane Goodall</PERSON> famous?
749 What made <PERSON>Jane Goodall</PERSON> famous?
750 Define thalassemia.
751 What is the meaning of thalassemia?
752 How is thalassemia defined?
753 What soft drink is most heavily caffeinated?
754 What is the most heavily caffeinated soft drink?
755 To get the most caffeine, what soda should I drink?
756 Which type of soda has the greatest amount of caffeine?
757 What soft drink would provide me with the biggest intake of caffeine?
758 What is the collective term for geese?
759 What is the collective noun for geese?
760 What is the term for a group of geese?
761 What is the name given to a group of geese?
762 What is the gestation period for human pregnancies?
763 How long is human gestation?
764 What is the gestation period for humans?
765 A normal human pregnancy lasts how many months?
766 What was the alternate to <ORGANIZATION>VHS</ORGANIZATION>?
767 What video format was an alternative to VHS?
768 What format was the major competition of VHS?
769 What ethnic group introduced the idea of potlatch?
770 What is the cultural origin of the ceremony of potlatch?
771 Who developed potlatch?
772 Where is <LOCATION>Logan Airport</LOCATION>?
773 What city is <LOCATION>Logan Airport</LOCATION> in?
774 <ORGANIZATION>Logan International</ORGANIZATION> serves what city?
775 <LOCATION>Logan International</LOCATION> is located in what city?
776 What city's airport is named <LOCATION>Logan International</LOCATION>?
777 What city is served by <LOCATION>Logan International Airport</LOCATION>?
778 <PERSON>Woodrow Wilson</PERSON> was president of which university?
780 <PERSON>Woodrow Wilson</PERSON> served as president of what university?
781 What does the acronym CPR mean?
782 What do the initials CPR stand for?
783 CPR is the abbreviation for what?
784 What is the meaning of "CPR"?
785 What was the name of <PERSON>Darth Vader</PERSON>'s son?
786 What was <ORGANIZATION>Darth Vader</ORGANIZATION>'s son named?
787 What caused the death of <PERSON>Bob Marley</PERSON>?
788 What killed <PERSON>Bob Marley</PERSON>?
789 What was the cause of <PERSON>Bob Marley</PERSON>'s death?
790 What instrument does <PERSON>Ray Charles</PERSON> play?
791 Musician <PERSON>Ray Charles</PERSON> plays what instrument?
792 <PERSON>Ray Charles</PERSON> plays which instrument?
793 <PERSON>Ray Charles</PERSON> is best known for playing what instrument?
794 When was <PERSON>Dick Clark</PERSON> born?
795 When is <PERSON>Dick Clark</PERSON>'s birthday?
796 What is <PERSON>Dick Clark</PERSON>'s date of birth?
797 What was <PERSON>Poe</PERSON>'s birthplace?
798 What was the birthplace of <PERSON>Edgar Allen Poe</PERSON>?
799 Where is <PERSON>Poe</PERSON>'s birthplace?
800 What monarch signed the <ORGANIZATION>Magna Carta</ORGANIZATION>?
801 Which king signed the <ORGANIZATION>Magna Carta</ORGANIZATION>?
802 Who was the king who was forced to agree to the <ORGANIZATION>Magna Carta</ORGANIZATION>?
803 What king signed the <ORGANIZATION>Magna Carta</ORGANIZATION>?
804 Who was the king who signed the <ORGANIZATION>Magna Carta</ORGANIZATION>?
805 Where is one's corpus callosum found?
806 What part of your body contains the corpus callosum?
807 The corpus callosum is in what part of the body?
808 What English word has the most letters?
809 What English word contains the most letters?
810 What is the longest English word?
811 What is the name of the inventor of silly putty?
812 Silly putty was invented by whom?
813 Who was the inventor of silly putty?
814 When was <LOCATION>Berlin</LOCATION>'s <ORGANIZATION>Brandenburg</ORGANIZATION> gate erected?
815 What is the date of Boxing Day?
816 What date is Boxing Day?
817 Boxing Day is celebrated on what date?
818 What city does <LOCATION>McCarren Airport</LOCATION> serve?
819 What city is served by <LOCATION>McCarren Airport</LOCATION>?
820 McCarren Airport is located in what city?
821 What is the location of <LOCATION>McCarren Airport</LOCATION>?
822 Where is <LOCATION>McCarren Airport</LOCATION> located?
823 Who invented "The Muppets"?
824 What was the name of "The Muppets" creator?
825 "The Muppets" was created by whom?
826 Name the creator of "The Muppets".
827 Who is the creator of "The Muppets"?
828 What is the date of Bastille Day?
829 Bastille Day occurs on which date?
830 What is the equivalent of the <ORGANIZATION>Red Cross</ORGANIZATION> in the <LOCATION>Middle East</LOCATION>?
831 What is the name of the Islamic counterpart to the <ORGANIZATION>Red Cross</ORGANIZATION>?
832 Name the Islamic counterpart to the <ORGANIZATION>Red Cross</ORGANIZATION>.
833 What is the Islamic equivalent of the <ORGANIZATION>Red Cross</ORGANIZATION>?
834 What is the name given to the Islamic counterpart of the <ORGANIZATION>Red Cross</ORGANIZATION>?
835 <PERSON>Colin Powell</PERSON> is most famous for what?
836 <PERSON>Colin Powell</PERSON> is best known for what achievement?
837 Who is <PERSON>Colin Powell</PERSON>?
838 <PERSON>Colin Powell</PERSON> is famous for what?
839 What time of year do most people fly?
840 What time of year has the most air travel?
841 What time of year is air travel the heaviest?
842 At what time of year is air travel at a peak?
843 Name a golf course in <LOCATION>Myrtle Beach</LOCATION>.
844 What is <LOCATION>Pittsburg</LOCATION>'s baseball team called?
845 The major league baseball team in <LOCATION>Pittsburgh</LOCATION> is called what?
846 Name <LOCATION>Pittsburgh</LOCATION>'s baseball team.
847 What city is the <ORGANIZATION>Orange Bowl</ORGANIZATION> in?
848 The <ORGANIZATION>Orange Bowl</ORGANIZATION> is in what city?
849 The <ORGANIZATION>Orange Bowl</ORGANIZATION> is located in what city?
850 Where is the <ORGANIZATION>Orange Bowl</ORGANIZATION>?
851 When did <LOCATION>Mount St. Helens</LOCATION> last erupt?
852 When did <LOCATION>Mount St. Helen</LOCATION> last have a major eruption?
853 When did <LOCATION>Mount St. Helen</LOCATION> last have a significant eruption?
854 How do you abbreviate "Original Equipment Manufacturer"?
855 How is "Original Equipment Manufacturer" abbreviated?
856 Where can one find Rider College?
857 What is the location of <ORGANIZATION>Rider College</ORGANIZATION>?
858 Rider College is located in what city?
859 Where is <ORGANIZATION>Rider College</ORGANIZATION>?
860 What is the occupation of <PERSON>Nicholas Cage</PERSON>?
861 What is <PERSON>Nicholas Cage</PERSON>'s profession?
862 What is <PERSON>Nicholas Cage</PERSON>'s occupation?
863 What does caliente translate to in English?
864 What is the English meaning of caliente?
865 What is the meaning of caliente (in English)?
866 What is the English translation for the word "caliente"?
867 What is the Jewish alphabet called?
868 The Jewish alphabet is called what?
869 The Jewish alphabet is known as what?
870 <PERSON>Jackson Pollock</PERSON> was a native of what country?
871 <PERSON>Jackson Pollock</PERSON> is of what nationality?
872 What was the nationality of <PERSON>Jackson Pollock</PERSON>?
873 The <ORGANIZATION>Kentucky Horse Park</ORGANIZATION> is close to which <LOCATION>American</LOCATION> city?
874 Where is the <LOCATION>Kentucky Horse Park</LOCATION> located?
875 Where is the <LOCATION>Kentucky Horse Park</LOCATION>?
876 What city is the <LOCATION>Kentucky Horse Park</LOCATION> near?
877 The <LOCATION>Kentucky Horse Park</LOCATION> is located near what city?
878 What is a nickname for <LOCATION>Mississippi</LOCATION>?
879 <LOCATION>Mississippi</LOCATION> is nicknamed what?
880 <LOCATION>Mississippi</LOCATION> has what name for a state nickname?
881 What is the nickname for the state of <LOCATION>Mississippi</LOCATION>?
882 What is the nickname of the state of <LOCATION>Mississippi</LOCATION>?
883 Rotary engines were manufactured by which company?
884 Who made the rotary engine automobile?
885 Rotary engine cars were made by what company?
886 Rotary engines used to be made by whom?
887 What company produced rotary engine vehicles?
888 What is the world's highest peak?
889 What is the highest mountain in the world?
890 Name the highest mountain.
891 What is the name of the tallest mountain in the world?
892 What makes <LOCATION>Black Hills</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>South Dakota</LOCATION> a tourist attraction?
893 What are the <LOCATION>Black Hills</LOCATION> known for?
